pikciochain.com 2018-07-28

# Privacy Policy

Privacy Policy
Date of last revision April 20, 2016
-----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------
MatchupBox, Inc. ("MatchupBox", “We”, “Our”) is committed to respecting the privacy
rights and concerns of all users of our websites ("Sites"), applications, mobile applications
and services (collectively, the "Services"). Privacy compliance is precisely the core of our
activities. As such, we have established and implemented this privacy policy to set forth
MatchupBox’ policy with respect to information including personally identifiable data
(“Personal Data”) and other information that is collected from visitors to the Sites and
Services. If you have any questions regarding this information or our privacy practices, please
see the section entitled "Questions? Contact Us" at the end of this privacy policy.
What information does MatchupBox, Inc. collect?
When you interact with us through the Services, we may collect Personal Data and other
information from you, as further described below:
Personal Data that you provide through the Services:
We collect Personal Data from you when you voluntarily provide such information, such as
when you contact us with inquiries, respond to one of our surveys, register for access to the
Services or use certain Services. Wherever MatchupBox collects Personal Data we make an
effort to provide a link to this Privacy Policy.
By voluntarily providing us with Personal Data, you are consenting to our use of it in
accordance with this Privacy Policy. If you provide Personal Data to the Services, you
acknowledge and agree that such Personal Data may be transferred from your current
location to the offices and servers of MatchupBox.
Other Information:
Non-Identifiable Data: When you interact with MatchupBox through the Services, we receive
and store certain personally non-identifiable information. Such information, which is
collected passively using various technologies, cannot presently be used to specifically
identify you. MatchupBox may store such information itself or such information may be
included in databases owned and maintained by MatchupBox affiliates, agents or service
providers. The Services may use such information and pool it with other information to track,
for example, the total number of visitors to our Site, the number of visitors to each page of our
Site, and the domain names of our visitors' Internet service providers. It is important to note
that no Personal Data is available or used in this process.
In operating the Services, we use a technology called "cookies" regarding the Twitter
functionality. A cookie is a piece of information that the computer that hosts our Services
gives to your browser when you access the Services. We only add cookies to help providing a
Twitter functionality to the Services. In this only case where we use cookies, we will not
collect Personal Data except with your permission. On most web browsers, you will find a

“help” section on the toolbar. Please refer to this section for information on how to receive
notification when you are receiving a new cookie and how to turn cookies off. If you turn
cookies off, it will have no consequences to take advantage of the Services features.
Aggregated Personal Data: In an ongoing effort to better understand and serve the users of the
Services, MatchupBox often conducts research on its customer demographics, interests and
behavior based on the Personal Data and other information provided to us. This research may
be compiled and analyzed on an aggregate basis. MatchupBox may share this aggregate data
with its affiliates and agents. MatchupBox don’t share this aggregate data with and business
partners. This aggregate information does not identify you personally. MatchupBox may also
disclose aggregated user statistics in order to describe our services to current and prospective
business partners, and to other third parties for other lawful purposes.
How does MatchupBox use the information collected?
MatchupBox uses the Personal Data you provide in a manner that is consistent with this
Privacy Policy. If you provide Personal Data for a certain reason, we may use the Personal
Data in connection with the reason for which it was provided. For instance, if you contact us
by email, we will use the Personal Data you provide to answer your question or resolve your
problem. Also, if you provide Personal Data in order to obtain access to the Services, we will
use your Personal Data to provide you with access to such services and to monitor your use of
such services. MatchupBox and its subsidiaries and affiliates (the “Related Companies”) may
also use your Personal Data and other personally non-identifiable information collected
through the Services to help us improve the content and functionality of the Services, to better
understand our users and to improve the Services. MatchupBox and its affiliates may use this
information to contact you in the future to tell you about services we believe will be of
interest to you. If we do so, each marketing communication we send you will contain
instructions permitting you to "opt-out" of receiving future marketing communications. In
addition, if at any time you wish not to receive any future marketing communications or you
wish to have your name deleted from our mailing lists, please contact us as indicated below.
If MatchupBox intends on using any Personal Data in any manner that is not consistent with
this Privacy Policy, you will be informed of such anticipated use prior to or at the time at
which the Personal Data is collected
How does MatchupBox disclose Your Personal Data and Other
Information?
MatchupBox is not in the business of selling your information. We consider this information
to be a vital part of our relationship with you. There are, however, certain circumstances in
which we may share your Personal Data with certain third parties without further notice to
you, as set forth below:
Business Transfers: As we develop our business, we might sell or buy businesses or assets. In
the event of a corporate sale, merger, reorganization, dissolution or similar event, Personal
Data may be part of the transferred assets.
Related Companies: We may also share your Personal Data with our Related Companies for
purposes consistent with this Privacy Policy.

Agents, Consultants and Related Third Parties: MatchupBox, like many businesses,
sometimes hires other companies to perform certain business-related functions. Examples of
such functions include mailing information, maintaining databases and processing payments.
When we employ another entity to perform a function of this nature, we only provide them
with the information that they need to perform their specific function.
Legal Requirements: MatchupBox may disclose your Personal Data if required to do so by
law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to (i) comply with a legal
obligation, (ii) protect and defend the rights or property of MatchupBox, (iii) act in urgent
circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of the Services or the public, or (iv)
protect against legal liability.
Exclusions
This Privacy Policy does not apply to any Personal Data collected by MatchupBox other than
Personal Data collected through the Services. This Privacy Policy shall not apply to any
unsolicited information you provide to MatchupBox through the Services or through any
other means. This includes, but is not limited to, information posted to any public areas of the
Services, such as forums, any ideas for new products or modifications to existing products,
and other unsolicited submissions (collectively, “Unsolicited Information”). All Unsolicited
Information shall be deemed to be non-confidential and MatchupBox shall be free to
reproduce, use, disclose, and distribute such Unsolicited Information to others without
limitation or attribution.
Third party links and co-brand relationships
This Privacy Policy applies only to the Services. The Services may contain links to other web
sites not operated or controlled by MatchupBox (the “Third Party Sites”). The policies and
procedures we described here do not apply to the Third Party Sites. The links from the
Services do not imply that MatchupBox endorses or has reviewed the Third Party Sites. We
suggest contacting those sites directly for information on their privacy policies.
Security
MatchupBox takes reasonable steps to protect the Personal Data provided via the Services
from loss, misuse, and unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration, or destruction. However, no
Internet or email transmission is ever fully secure or error free. In particular, email sent to or
from the Services may not be secure. Therefore, you should take special care in deciding what
information you send to us via email. Please keep this in mind when disclosing any Personal
Data to MatchupBox via the Internet.
Other Agreements, Terms and Conditions
Your access to and use of the Services is subject to any additional agreements, terms and
conditions between you and MatchupBox.
Special note to parents
In compliance with the 1998 Children's Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA), the Sites are
general audience websites, and do not knowingly collect, nor will it ever knowingly retain,

personally identifiable information from any visitor MatchupBox actually knows to be under
thirteen years of age without the consent of that child's parent or legal guardian.
Notification of changes
The Services and our business may change from time to time. As a result, at times it may be
necessary for MatchupBox to make changes to this Privacy Policy. MatchupBox reserves the
right to update or modify this Privacy Policy at any time and from time to time without prior
notice. Please review this policy periodically, and especially before you provide any Personal
Data. This Privacy Policy was last updated on the date indicated above. Your continued use of
the Services after any changes or revisions to this Privacy Policy shall indicate your
agreement with the terms of such revised Privacy Policy.
Access to information
To keep your Personal Data accurate, current, and complete, please contact us as specified
below. We will take reasonable steps to update or correct Personal Data in our possession that
you have previously submitted via the Services.
Questions? Contact us.
If you have any questions about our privacy practices, please do not hesitate to write to us at:
Privacy Matters c/o MatchupBox, Inc. 50 Milk Street 16th Floor Boston MA 02109 Or send
us an email at: privacymatters@matchupbox.com
